{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435035707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435035707"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435036095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435036094"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435036329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435036328"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435036645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435036645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435036881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435036881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435040327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435040327"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435040621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435040621"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435041525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435041525"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435041948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435041948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435044832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435044831"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435045115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435045114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435045959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435045959"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435046622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435046622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435047355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435047355"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435047681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435047680"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435047954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435047954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435048268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435048267"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435048531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435048531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435052285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435052285"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435052672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435052671"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435052905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435052905"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435053218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435053218"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435053452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435053452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435056931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435056931"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435057224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435057224"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435058128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435058127"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435058559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435058558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435061466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435061466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435061756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435061756"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435062608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435062607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435063283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435063282"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435064030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435064029"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435064363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435064363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435064648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435064648"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435064972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435064972"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435065247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435065247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435068694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435068692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435068792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435068792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" f205b90b-644c-4f6d-abee-d46a87789ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435081553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435081553"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435082151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435082150"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435083237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435083237"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435084235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435084234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435084428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435084427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435084881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435084881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435085629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435085628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435086594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435086593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435089008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435089007"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435089664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435089664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435090841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435090840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435091789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435091789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435092557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435092557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435093365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435093364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" WAPENZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435094187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435094186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435097029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435097028"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435098104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435098103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435098738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435098738"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435099524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435099523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435100057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435100056"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435100442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435100442"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435100977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435100977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435101373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435101372"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435102901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435102894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" ILIMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435103440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435103439"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435104355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435104355"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435107597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435107596"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435108806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435108806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435109518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435109517"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435110002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435110001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435110889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435110889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" UKAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435111414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435111413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435112305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435112304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435114607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435114607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435115895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435115895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" NIANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435116794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435116793"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435117273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435117272"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435117971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435117970"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435118384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435118383"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435121385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435121385"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435121869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435121868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435122623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435122623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435123418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435123418"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435123994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435123994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435124804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435124803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435127765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435127765"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435128651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435128650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435130147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435130147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" SIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435132498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435132497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435133141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435133140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435134196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435134195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435135005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435135004"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435135892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435135891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" UKIWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435136628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435136627"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" MEKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435139492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435139491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435139550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435139549"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435143228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435143227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435143643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435143642"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435144277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435144276"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435145094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435145093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435145819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435145819"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435146666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435146665"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435149035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435149035"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" FYATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435149873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435149872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" ULIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435150385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435150384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435150736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435150735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435153261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435153259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435154786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435154785"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435157908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435157908"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435158523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435158522"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435159305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435159304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435160145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435160145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435160510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435160509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435161137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435161136"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" KUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435161611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435161611"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435162428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435162427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435165638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435165637"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435166511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435166511"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" YALIPOANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435167415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435167415"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" KUCHEMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435169413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435169413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435169916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435169915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435172575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435172575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435173172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435173171"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435173544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435173544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435174720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435174719"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" IKACHOMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435175182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435175181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435175705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435175704"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435176138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435176137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435177173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435177172"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" UKAKATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435179825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435179825"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435180428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435180428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" BADALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435180631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435180631"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435181667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435181666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" KUMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435181871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435181871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435182265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435182264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435182910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435182910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435183324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435183324"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435184001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435184000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435185259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435185258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435185524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435185524"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435186131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435186130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435186959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435186958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435187616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435187616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435190113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435190112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435190231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435190231"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435200604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435200603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 573abd17-9db4-4d0c-a2d3-3d9d9d861b48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435212134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435212134"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435214696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435214696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435218967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435218967"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435222247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435222247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435226518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435226518"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435229217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435229217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435234017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435234017"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435245815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435245815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435247788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435247788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435257526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435257526"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435269306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435269306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435270835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435270835"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435273988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435273988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435278951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435278951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435283179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435283179"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435285648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435285648"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435290381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435290381"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435292875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435292875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435297052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435297052"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435298760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435298760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435303288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435303288"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435313419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435313419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435315389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435315388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435322031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435322031"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" a104c4ce-fbb4-4117-9353-8a6d0865f22c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435334246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435334246"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435335282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435335281"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435336630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435336629"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435337496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435337495"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435338435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435338433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435339023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435339023"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435339937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435339936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435343389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435343389"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435343970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435343969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435344688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435344687"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435345282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435345282"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435345466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435345466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435346703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435346702"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435350372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435350371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435350863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435350862"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435351680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435351679"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435352653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435352652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" ULIOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435356039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435356039"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435356614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435356613"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435357331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435357330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435357922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435357921"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435358106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435358105"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435359339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435359338"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435363048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435363047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANATANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435363843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435363843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435364567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435364567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435365664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435365663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435366238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435366238"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435369598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435369597"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435370177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435370176"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435370892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435370892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435371477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435371476"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435371659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435371658"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435372892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435372892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435376975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435376975"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435377681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435377681"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435378283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435378282"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435378532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435378532"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435379548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435379548"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" MABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435380205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435380204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435383712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435383711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435384285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435384285"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435385002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435385001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435385586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435385586"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435385769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435385769"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435387005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435387005"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435390471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435390471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435390934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435390933"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435391528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435391528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435391798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435391798"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435392656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435392655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435392808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435392808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435393494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435393493"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435396886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435396885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435397458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435397458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435398170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435398170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435398764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435398763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435398949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435398948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435400188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435400187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435403623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435403622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPIGA"," userResponse":" ANAPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435404507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435404507"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435405101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435405100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435405674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435405673"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435405947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435405947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435406792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435406791"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435407471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435407471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" AINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435407758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435407757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435408705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435408704"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHANO"," userResponse":" LUGHANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435412074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435412074"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435412647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435412647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435413361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435413360"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435413950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435413950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435414132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435414132"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435415368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435415368"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435418668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435418668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435419040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435419039"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435419593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435419593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435420465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435420464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435423823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435423822"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435424398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435424398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435425113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435425113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435425695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435425695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435425879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435425879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435427113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435427113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435430424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435430424"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435431080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435431080"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435431204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435431204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435431687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435431686"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435432051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435432050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435432696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435432696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435432848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435432848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435433809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435433808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435437212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435437211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435437785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435437785"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435438502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435438501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435439084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435439084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435439267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435439267"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435440505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435440504"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435443834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435443833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435444629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435444628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435445254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435445254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435446110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435446109"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEUSI"," userResponse":" VYEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435449621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435449621"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435450197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435450196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435450913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435450913"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435451494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435451494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435451671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435451671"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435452907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435452907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435456213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435456213"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435456908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435456907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435458064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435458063"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435461499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435461499"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435462071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435462071"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435462789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435462788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435463375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435463374"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435463558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435463557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435464794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435464794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435468573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435468573"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" ANAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435469408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435469407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435469591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435469591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435470958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435470956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAYANSI"," userResponse":" SAYANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435471730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435471730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435473160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435473159"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJAMII"," userResponse":" KIJAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435473614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435473613"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435474500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435474499"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HESABU"," userResponse":" HESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435477863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435477862"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435478437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435478436"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435479152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435479152"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435479736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435479735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435479917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435479917"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435481147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435481146"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435484515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435484513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435484789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435484789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435485698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435485697"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435487833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435487833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," userResponse":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435489062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435489061"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435489344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435489343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435489981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435489980"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435490205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435490204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435490838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435490837"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435494172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435494171"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435494747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435494747"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435495463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435495463"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435496053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435496052"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435496236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435496235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435497472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435497471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435500104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435500102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435500167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435500167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 34bcbbfe-65e1-4fda-a328-d705e2924b1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435512665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435512664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435513701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435513700"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435515047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435515047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435515912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435515911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435516847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435516846"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435517435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435517435"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435518347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435518346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435521827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435521826"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435522399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435522399"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435523115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435523114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435523699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435523698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435523878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435523877"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435525112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435525112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435528735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435528735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435529229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435529228"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435530047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435530047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435531022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435531021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" ULIOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435534402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435534401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435534974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435534974"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435535690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435535690"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435536274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435536273"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435536461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435536460"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435537695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435537695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435541386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435541385"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANATANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435542181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435542181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435542913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435542912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435544010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435544009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435544584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435544583"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435547941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435547941"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435548516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435548515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435549233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435549232"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435549819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435549818"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435550002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435550002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435551239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435551238"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435555272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435555271"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435555979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435555978"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435556585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435556584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435556839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435556838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435557854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435557854"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" MABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435558509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435558508"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435562012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435562012"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435562588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435562587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435563303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435563303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435563885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435563885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435564069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435564069"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435565304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435565304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435568738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435568738"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435569203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435569203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435569801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435569800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435570073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435570073"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435570928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435570928"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435571082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435571081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435571767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435571766"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435575211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435575210"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435575786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435575785"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435576501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435576501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435577084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435577084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435577266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435577266"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435578503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435578502"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435581878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435581877"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPIGA"," userResponse":" ANAPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435582761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435582761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435583356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435583355"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435583931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435583930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435584203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435584202"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435585048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435585047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435585724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435585723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" AINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435586009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435586009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435586957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435586956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHANO"," userResponse":" LUGHANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435590333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435590332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435590916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435590914"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435591633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435591632"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435592221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435592221"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435592402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435592402"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435593638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435593638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435596944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435596944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435597318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435597317"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435597872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435597872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435598745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435598745"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435602102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435602102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435602676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435602675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435603389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435603389"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435603977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435603976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435604157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435604156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435605393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435605392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435608667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435608666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435609324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435609323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435609450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435609450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435609932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435609931"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435610295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435610294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435610941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435610940"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435611095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435611094"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435612060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435612059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435615427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435615427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435616000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435616000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435616716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435616715"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435617308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435617307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435617491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435617490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435618728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435618728"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435622072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435622072"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435622870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435622870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435623498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435623497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435624350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435624350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEUSI"," userResponse":" VYEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435627851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435627851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435628430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435628430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435629147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435629147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435629730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435629730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435629914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435629914"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435631144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435631144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435634459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435634458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435635153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435635153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435636306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435636306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435639724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435639724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435640297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435640296"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435641012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435641012"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435641602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435641601"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435641786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435641786"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435643021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435643020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435646717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435646716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" ANAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435647551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435647550"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435647733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435647733"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435649099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435649099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAYANSI"," userResponse":" SAYANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435649877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435649876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435651304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435651303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJAMII"," userResponse":" KIJAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435651758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435651758"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435652645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435652645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HESABU"," userResponse":" HESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435655978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435655977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435656561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435656560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435657275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435657274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435657861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435657860"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435658041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435658041"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435659277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435659276"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435662646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435662646"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435662918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435662918"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435663826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435663825"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435665962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435665962"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," userResponse":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435667189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435667188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435667471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435667471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435668111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435668111"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435668336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435668335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435668972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435668971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435672271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435672269"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435672846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435672845"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435673562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435673561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435674147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435674147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435674332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435674331"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435675569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435675568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435678226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435678225"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435678320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435678319"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 5fdf057c-86c6-4ffb-8954-0e1a3752c38e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435691492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435691491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435694120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435694120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435695730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435695730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435698187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435698186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435699760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435699760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435704957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435704957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435706590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435706589"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435709519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435709519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435711134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435711133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435715458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435715458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435717091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435717090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435721336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435721336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435722956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435722955"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435726245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435726245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435727863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435727863"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435730763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435730762"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435732789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435732788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435732876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435732876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" d05c84d8-bfc9-475e-8041-91adc290c3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435744794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435744794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435749211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435749211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435754285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435754285"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435759069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435759069"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435764801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435764801"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435770047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435770047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435776240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435776240"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435780264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435780264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435783374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435783374"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435787492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435787492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435789910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435789909"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435793720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435793720"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435795616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435795616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435802579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435802579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435804544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435804543"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435813618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435813618"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 7756c4d6-112f-498a-86d1-c43082f7fa56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435823127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435823127"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-e-u"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435826921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435826920"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_i-o-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435831229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435831229"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435834800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435834800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_i-o-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435838329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435838329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-u-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435841747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435841747"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-u-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435845190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435845189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-u-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435848719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435848718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-a-o"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435852326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435852325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-a-u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435856051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435856051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_e-u-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435861794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435861793"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_e-u-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435986012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435986011"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 87f7b4b8-9aa7-4eb1-b0b5-49252d1f47c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_e-u-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435986114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435986114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 9e510f58-c53d-42f4-967e-bf4785fa468e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435996143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435996143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548435999723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548435999723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-a-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436003363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436003363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436007142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436007142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436011125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436011125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436027045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436027045"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_e-u-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436033566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436033565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_e-u-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436043406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436043406"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-o"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436047198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436047198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-u-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436062725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436062724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436068476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436068475"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 049a41f0-19dd-4cf3-bbee-8b991b3d5221"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436079577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436079577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436081089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436081089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436081354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436081354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436083157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436083157"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436084918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436084918"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436086430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436086430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436090822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436090822"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436099392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436099392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436099512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436099512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436103152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436103151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436106117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436106117"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436109406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436109406"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436113157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436113157"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436116575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436116575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436124667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436124667"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436128674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436128674"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436132587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436132587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436138876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436138876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436146088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436146088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436153932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436153931"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436155943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436155942"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_195017"," gameId":" 21b5c8aa-02d0-4e42-b305-0297a77cb9b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}